A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of Economic Development, 1986-1993.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Secretary of Economic Development,
1986-1993.
The Library of Virginia
33720, 34595, 35483, 35643
Virginia. Secretary of Economic Development.
XX cu. ft. (XX boxes)
Administrative Information
Arranged by series.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 33720 was transferred by the Secretary of Economic Development, February 1, 1990.
Accession 34595 was transferred by the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, March 16, 1994.
Accession 35483 was transferred by the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, August 27, 1997.
Accession 35643 was transferred by the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, January 12, 1998.
Historical Information
In 1986 the Secretary of Commerce and Resources was dissolved and split into two separate offices, the Secretary of Economic Development and the Secretary of Natural Resources. In 1994 the name of the office of the Secretary of Economic Development was changed to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade. The Secretary of Economic Development was responsible for assisting the Governor in implementing policies for promoting economic development, providing managerial guidance and direction to economic development agencies, and developing and promoting economic development programs and budgets.
Scope and Content
Records, 1986-1993, of the Secretary of Economic Development. The correspondence documents the development, establishment and implementation of policies and procedures implementing the Secretary's mandate on the behalf of the Governor. The records consist of incoming and outgoing correspondence, reports, memoranda, budget documents and related materials. The collection is arranged into four sections by accession number. For earlier records see Secretary of Commerce and Resources; for later records see Secretary of Commerce and Trade.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following sections:
Records, 1986-1989 (33720); Records, 1986-1993 (34595); Records,1990-1993 (35483); Records, 1992-1993 (35643)
Contents List
- Records, 1986-1989 (Accession 33720)., Extent: 3 cubic feet (3 boxes). (Box 1-3)
  Richard M. Bagley was Secretary of Economic Development, 1986-1988 and Curry A. Roberts served as the Secretary of Economic Development, 1988-1990. These records were created during the Gov. Baliles Administration.
  - Dept. of Economic Development.
    - Airline Hubs, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - American Airlines Flights (Raleigh-Durham-London), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Appropriations Act, 1987. (Box 1)
    - Arab Nations (Import/Export), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Research Corporation, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Ball, Robert B. (Tourism and Economic Development Committees), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - BASF Corporation (Williamsburg, Va.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Babcock and Wilson, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Bath County, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Bear Island Paper Co., 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Bell Canada, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Bi-Annual Report of the Secretary of Economic Deveolpment, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - British Aerospace, Inc., 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Canada (General) - Bell Canada, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Canada (General) - Intertape Systems, Inc., 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Canada (General) - Rolph Clark Stone Packaging, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Canon, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Carnation Company (Danville, Va.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Celanese Dedication (Portsmouth, Va.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Charles City County Economic Development - Intertech, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Cheatham Annex Fuel Depot, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Community Certification, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Cook Family Foods, Ltd., 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Coors Company, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Crestar Financial Review, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Culpeper (Community Certification), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Dana Corp. Dedication, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Delaware, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Eco Knit (Patrick Co.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - EDS Tour (Fairfax Co.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Electronic Data Systems Corp. (Northern Va.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Federal Mogul, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Foreign Sales Corp., 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Forward Hampton Roads, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - George Mason University (Southwest Virginia Economic Development), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Gloucester Industrial Park, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co. (Danville, Va), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Hercules, Inc., 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Herndon Chamber of Commerce, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Hill Brothers Coffee, Inc., 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Historic Fredericksburg Foundation, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Historic Preservation and Economic Development, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Japan - General, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Japan - SEUS, 1986. (Box 1)
    - Journal of Commerce (Alison Bilow), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Mattaco, Inc. (Russell Co.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Merillat Industries, Inc. (Mt. Jackson, Va.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - New Businesses in Virginia (Economic Development), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - North American Reiss Corp., 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Northern Neck (Economic Development), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Orvis Company, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Pittsylvania County Certification, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Planning District Commission - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Powell, Kenneth, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Read Development Co. (Hampton, Va.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Schooner Alexandria (Alexandria Seaport Foundation), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Small Business and Financial Services Office, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Software Productivity Consortium, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Southside Planning District Commission, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Status Furniture Co. (Kenbridge, Va.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Tracking Letters, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - U.S. Sprint / Magnavox (Reston, Va.), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Venture Capital Proposal, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Business Council (Roster), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Virginia Center for World Trade, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Virginia State Bar (Law Week), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Wear-Ever (Proctor Silex), 1986-1989. (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Tourism.
    - General file, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Culture Key Program, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
    - Travel Authorizations, 1986-1989. (Box 1)
  - Virginia Employment Commission.
    - General file, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Annis, Kenny (Employment with Fruit Growers Assoc.), 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Mission Statement, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Regulation Review Summary, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Statewide Cost Allocation, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Tracking letters, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Trust Fund, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Foresty.
    - General file, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Mission Statement, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Regulatory Review Statement, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Housing and Community Development.
    - General file, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Appalachian Regional Commission, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Bonds, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Bonds (Tax-exempt), 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Fire Marshal (Padlocking of cells at State Penitentiary), 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Main Street Program, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority.
    - General file, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Lee Gardens (Northern Virginia), 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Multi-Family Housing Bonds, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Labor and Industry.
    - General file, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Mines, Minerals, and Energy.
    - United Coal Company (Stripper Wells), 1986-1989. (Box 2)
    - Shenandoah Quarries, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
  - Milk Commission.
    - General File, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
  - Minority Business Enterprise.
    - General File, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
  - Virginia Resourses Authority.
    - General File, 1986-1989. (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services.
    - DIT Study of VDACS, 1986-1989. (Box 3)
    - Farmers' Markets, 1986-1989. (Box 3)
    - James City Farmers' Markets, 1986-1989. (Box 3)
    - Livestock Exports, 1986-1989. (Box 3)
    - Orkin Pest Control Investigation (Galax, Va.), 1986-1989. (Box 3)
  - Arts Commission.
    - General File, 1986-1989. (Box 3)
  - Dept. of Commerce.
    - Accountancy Board, 1986-1989. (Box 3)
    - American Institute of Architects v. Hathcock, 1986-1989. (Box 3)
    - Architects, Professional Engineers and Land Surveyors, 1986-1989. (Box 3)
    - Architects, 1986-1989. (Box 3)
    - Real Estate Commission, 1986-1989. (Box 3)
- Records, 1990-1993 (Accession 34595)., Extent: 62 cubic feet (62 boxes). (Box 1-62)
  These records were created or collected during the administration of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1994, though some records may pre-date this time frame. During the Wilder Administration, Lawrence Framme, III, served as Secretary of Economic Development, 1990-1992, and Cathleen Magennis served as Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1993-1994.
  - Dept. of Economic Development.
    - AFL-CIO, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - Angola, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - Bass Masters Fishing Tournament, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - Center for Innovative Technology - Industry Awareness Study, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - Center for Innovative Technology - Project Streamline Study, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - Center for Innovative Technology - Space Group, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - Central American Summit, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Community certification, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Diamonstein Study Commission, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Foreign investments in Virginia, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Foreign Offices justification, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - Grant Thornton Study, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Helms, Walter Clyde, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Jetro, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Moscript Research / Development, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Northern Virginia economic conditions, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Resolution Trust Corp., 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Rotary International, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Rural Development Plan, 1990-1993. (Box 49)
    - Rural Development Plan, 1990. (Box 50)
    - Rural Development Plan - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1990. (Box 48)
    - Rural Virginia Development Foundation, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Seed Center, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Seed Capital Organization, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - SEUS-Japan, 1990. (Box 47)
    - SEUS-Korea, 1990-1992. (Box 47)
    - Small Business Advisory Council, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Small Business Financing Authority, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - Small Business Development Authority, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - South America, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Southside Economic Development Commission, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Southern Technology Council, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Super Collider, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Tourism - General correspondence, 1990 June-1991 Dec. (Box 32)
    - United Airlines Prospect - Correspondence, 1991 Feb-1992 July. (Box 1)
    - United Airlines Prospect - Proposals, 1991-1992. (Box 1)
    - United Airlines Prospect - Correspondence, 1991 Feb-Oct. (Box 2)
    - USS George Washington, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Virginia Center Stage, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Virginia-Japan Golf Classic, 1991. (Box 31)
    - Virginia Israel Commission, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Virginia Israel Commission, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Virginia Travel Council, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - Warner Hall, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - Welcome Center, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - West Virginia, 1990-1993. (Box 46)
    - World Cup Soccer Tournament, 1990-1993. (Box 32)
    - World Trade Council, 1990-1993. (Box 31)
    - California, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - Governor's Briefing Book - Regional Economic Summit, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - INC Council of Growing Companies, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - Legal aspects of doing business in Virginia, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - Petersburg Chamber of Commerce, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - Remote Sensing Center, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - Southwest Virginia Small Business Development Cetner, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - Tax regulation discouraging business in Virginia, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - Virginia in the global economy, 1990-1993. (Box 33)
    - VEDCORP - Virginia Economic Development Corp., 1989 Sept-1991 Feb. (Box 33)
    - General correspondence, 1991 Jan-1992 Dec. (Box 34)
    - General correspondence, 1990 Jan-Dec. (Box 35)
    - Report to Top Management, 1991. (Box 35)
    - Tracking letters (4327-4742), 1990-1993. (Box 40)
    - Redskins Stadium (Constituent letters), 1992. (Box 45)
  - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services.
    - General correspondence, 1990-1992. (Box 3)
    - Tracking letters (#462-917), 1990-1993. (Box 3)
    - Tracking letters (No #s), 1990-1992. (Box 3)
    - Coyote control, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Diversification of agriculture, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Drought disaster, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Endangered Species Act, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - English Holly Orchards, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Endive industry, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Farm Bill, 1990. (Box 4)
    - Farmers markets, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Furadan, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Gypsy moth, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Marketing Division, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Meat and poultry inspection, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Pierce, Steward W., 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Seafood Task Force, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Horse Center, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Warrenton Lab tour, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Wine industry, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - Yarden Farms, 1990-1992. (Box 4)
    - General correspondence, 1988 Oct-1991 Jan. (Box 5)
    - Aquaculture, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
    - Agribusiness Council, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
    - Agribusiness Park study, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
    - Agriculture Development Authority, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
    - Ambassador Hatano's visit, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
    - Audit reports, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
    - Avian flu, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
    - Bloomingdale's promotion, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
    - Blue Ridge Fisheries, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
    - Center for International Trade, 1988-1991. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation.
    - General correspondence, 1989 May-1992 May. (Box 6)
    - Asbestos, 1989-1992. (Box 6)
    - Audit reports, 1989-1992. (Box 6)
    - Board of Contractors, 1989-1992. (Box 6)
    - Cosmotology Board, 1989-1992. (Box 6)
    - Digital Equipment Corp., 1989-1992. (Box 6)
    - Director's position, 1989-1992. (Box 6)
    - Polygraph Act, 1989-1992. (Box 6)
    - Private security industry, 1989-1992. (Box 6)
    - Private security fees, 1989-1992. (Box 6)
    - Shrink/swell soil, 1989-1992. (Box 6)
  - Virginia Employment Commission.
    - General correspondence, 1990 May-1992 Mar. (Box 7)
    - Advisory Council members, 1990-1992. (Box 7)
    - Audit reports, 1990-1992. (Box 7)
    - GATB testing, 1990-1992. (Box 7)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Dept., 1990-1992. (Box 7)
    - Job Shuttle Service, 1990-1992. (Box 7)
    - Labor Market Reports, 1990-1992. (Box 7)
    - Suffolk Office, 1990-1992. (Box 7)
    - Targeted Jobs Tax Credit, 1990-1992. (Box 7)
    - Unemployment insurance, 1990-1992. (Box 7)
  - Dept. of Forestry.
    - Tracking letters (#2814-4717), 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - General correspondence, 1990 Jan-1991 Mar. (Box 8)
    - Administrative Office Building, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Aircraft use, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - American Chestnut Foundation, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Audit reports, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Ban on burning, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Best management practices, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - CSX management practices, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Legal protection, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Property transfer, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Publications, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Timer Bridge Initiative, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Travel, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Tech, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
  - Dept. of Housing and Commnity Development.
    - General correspondence, 1990 Jan-1992 Jan. (Box 9)
    - Affordable housing loans, 1990-1992. (Box 9)
    - Asbestos study, 1990-1992. (Box 9)
    - Appalachian Regional Commission, 1990 Feb-1992 Jan. (Box 9)
    - Audit reports, 1990-1992. (Box 9)
    - Banks and lending practices, 1990-1992. (Box 9)
    - Building Code, 1990-1992. (Box 9)
    - Comprehensive Housing and Affordability Strategy (CHAS), 1990-1992. (Box 9)
    - Coldwell-Wilcox, 1990-1992. (Box 9)
    - Community Block Grants, 1990-1992. (Box 10)
    - Community for Opportunity Initiative, 1990-1992. (Box 10)
    - Earned Income Tax Credit, 1990-1992. (Box 10)
    - Eastern Shore Shopping Centers, 1990-1992. (Box 10)
    - Fire Marshal, 1990-1992. (Box 10)
    - Home Mortgage Disclosure Act, 1990-1992. (Box 10)
    - Housing consolidation, 1990-1992. (Box 10)
    - Housing Conference, 1991. (Box 11)
    - Housing Conference, 1990. (Box 11)
    - Industrial development bonds, 1990-1993. (Box 11)
    - Jackson Center (lease), 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Multifamily Rehabilitation Housing Loans, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Relocation of offices, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Septic tanks, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Southwest Virginia programs, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Coalition for the Homeless, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Community Development Corporation, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Housing Partnership Fund, 1990 Feb-1991 Nov. (Box 11)
    - Virginia Housing Study Commission, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
    - Weatherization Program, 1990-1991. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Housing Development Authority.
    - Tracking letters (2294-3551), 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - General correspondence, 1990 Jan-1991 Dec. (Box 12)
    - Evenson Dodge Report, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - Health-Tex, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - Mortgage insurance issues (HB 774), 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - Integrated housing, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - Multifamily housing bonds, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - Operation Bootstrap, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - Purchase of office building, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - Single family bonds, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - State Employee Home Purchase Program, 1990-1991. (Box 12)
  - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise.
    - Tracking letters (2767-3995), 1990-1991. (Box 12)
    - General correspondence, 1990 Jan-1991 Nov. (Box 12)
    - African Trade Conference, 1991. (Box 12)
    - African Trade Conference, 1990. (Box 12)
    - Audit reports, 1990-1991. (Box 13)
    - Cameroon Delegation, 1990-1991. (Box 13)
    - Disability entrepreneurship, 1990-1991. (Box 13)
    - Minority business procurement, 1990-1991. (Box 13)
    - VDOT contractors, 1990-1991. (Box 13)
  - Dept. of Labor and Industry.
    - Tracking letters (2819-3986), 1990-1991. (Box 13)
    - General correspondence, 1990 Jan-1992 Apr. (Box 13)
    - AFL-CIO apprenticeship, 1990-1992. (Box 13)
    - Apprenticeship Program, 1990-1992. (Box 13)
    - DIT Study of Management Property Purchase, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
    - Goddard Space Facility, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
    - Labor Center, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
    - Migrant workers, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
    - Occupational Health and Safety Administration (OSHA), 1990-1992. (Box 14)
    - Proposed accounting system, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
  - Milk Commission.
    - Tracking letters (814-1116), 1990-1992. (Box 14)
    - General correspondence, 1990 Jan-1992 Apr. (Box 14)
    - Audit reports, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
    - Director's position, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
    - Milk bid rigging, 1990-1992. (Box 14)
  - Dept. of Mines, Minerals and Energy.
    - General correspondence, 1990 Jan-1991 Dec. (Box 14)
    - Abandoned mines, 1990-1991. (Box 14)
    - Audit reports, 1990-1991. (Box 14)
    - Coal mining funding, 1990-1991. (Box 14)
    - Co-Generation, 1990-1991. (Box 14)
    - Directional mining, 1990-1991. (Box 14)
    - Gas and Oil Act, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Longwall Mining, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Mays Brothers, Inc., 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - News/Media, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Oil exploration, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Oil drilling ban, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Oil drilling - Westmoreland County, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Middle East Oil Crisis, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Oil overcharge, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Open supply issue, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Pittston Coal Company Strike, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Prison location, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Publications, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Relocation, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Tri-County Natural Gas, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - U.S. Windpower (Co-Generation Plant), 1990-1991. (Box 15)
    - Virginia Petroleum Council, 1990-1991. (Box 15)
  - Virginia Resources Authority.
    - Tracking letters (2039-2547), 1989-1992. (Box 16)
    - General correspondence, 1989 July-1992 Dec. (Box 16)
    - Audits, 1989-1992. (Box 16)
    - Virginia Water Project, 1989-1992. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Racing Commission.
    - General correspondence, 1991 Sept-1992 Dec. (Box 16)
    - Audits, 1991-1992. (Box 16)
    - Virginia Horse Center, 1991-1992. (Box 16)
  - Virginia Port Authority.
    - Tracking letters (257-3749), 1990-1991. (Box 16)
    - General correspondence, 1990 July-1991 Dec. (Box 16)
    - General correspondence, 1988 Mar-1990 July. (Box 17)
    - BOC Challenge, 1988-1991. (Box 17)
    - Bray, Bobby, 1988-1991. (Box 17)
    - General briefing material, 1988-1991. (Box 17)
    - Budget reductions, 1988-1991. (Box 17)
    - Competition, 1988-1991. (Box 17)
    - Construction Fund Allocation, 1988-1991. (Box 17)
    - Port of Richmond - General correspondence, 1987 July-1990 July. (Box 18)
    - Craney Island Study, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Debt Study, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Dredging of the Elizabeth River, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Eastern Bloc Ships, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Eva Airline Inaugural Function, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Foreign ship repairs, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Longshoreman's contracts, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Management Study of Organization (Touche Ross), 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Marketing position study, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Norfolk District Office - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Norfolk Internations Terminal (NIT), 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Norshipco, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Puerto Rico shipping potential, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Railcars - Northern Virginia, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Seawolf Shipbuilders, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Skyline Distribution Center, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Transportation (SJR 30), 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Role performance, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - Southern Tidewater Association of Ship Repairs, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - TRICON - Leased Soviet-owned ships, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
    - VPA Study of Future Operations, 1988-1991. (Box 19)
  - Dept. of World Trade.
    - General correspondence, 1989 July-1990 July. (Box 37)
    - General correspondence, 1990 Jan-June. (Box 40)
    - EC, 1992. (Box 40)
    - Foreign travel, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - IMP Awards, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - International Trade Council, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - Requested budget, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - U.S. / Canada trade, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - Visit from Egypt, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - Visit to Korea - Buying Mission, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - Visit to Saudi Arabia, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - Soviet Union, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - Tiawan, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - Virginia Business Council, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - Williamsburg planning meeting, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - Missions, 1990-1991. (Box 40)
    - World Trade Council, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
    - World Trade Council - Workshops, 1990-1992. (Box 40)
  - Tracking Letters.
    - Agriculture and Consumer Services, Dept. of (922-6497), 1990-1994. (Box 20)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of (2812-5401), 1990-1994. (Box 21)